https://anajet.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Ricoh Printing Systems America, Inc. (“RPSA, Inc.”) is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy Statement describes the information we collect from you, either online through this website, or social or mobile pages owned or operated by RPSA, Inc., whether accessed via computer, mobile device or other technology, or offline via your purchase of Ricoh DTG products, services, software, or other goods or interaction with RPSA, Inc. agents or employees (collectively Services), and how that information will be used. Please read this Privacy Policy Statement carefully, because by using the Services, you are acknowledging that you understand and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and consent to the manner in which we may collect, use and disclose the following information.
SECTION I. THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT
We and our service providers may collect information when you provide information to us and when information is collected automatically.
Personal Information. You may choose to give us personally identifiable information online to allow us to communicate with you, process your orders, or provide you with Services. Our online forms may ask for a small amount of relevant information, such as name, company name, email, street address, and phone number. Some forms may ask for a product serial number. If you make a purchase or order a repair, we may ask for your credit card number and billing information. Job applicants may be requested to provide information such as educational background, employment experience, and job interest.
Usage Information In addition to the information you may provide, we may collect information when you access or use the Services or a website “powered by” another company on behalf of AnaJet through our use of data collection technologies, including web beacons, cookies, and embedded web links. These technologies collect certain traffic information that your browser sends to a web site, such as your browser type and language, access times, and the address of the web site from which you arrived. They may also collect information about your Internet Protocol (IP) address.
SECTION II. RIGHT FOR DATA CONSENT AND USAGE
In compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation enacted on May, 25, 2018, users are permitted the option to request and obtain confirmation that data is or is not being collected and for what purpose. They are also afforded the option to withdraw consent for use and purge their personal data from our records within a reasonable timeframe. To make this request, please email gdprinfo@ricohdtg.com.
In compliance with the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”), effective January 1, 2020, California residents have expanded rights regarding the collection and disclosure of information. California residents have the right to learn what data is being collected on them that is stored and could be personally identifiable (e.g. name, email, phone, address, IP). California residents also have the right to request that the data be deleted and the right to request that the data not be sold to 3rd parties.
Verifiable California residents or their authorized representatives may make requests for data disclosure no more than twice in a 12-month period. Please direct questions and requests regarding your rights under the CCPA to info@ricohdtg.com.
SECTION III. RECORDING OF COMMUNICATIONS WITH RICOH PRINTING SYSTEMS AMERICA, INC.
IMPORTANT – PLEASE NOTE – All communications by and between RPSA, Inc. may be recorded or monitored for quality assurance, training and/or verification purposes. By engaging in any communication with AnaJet and its representatives, including without limitation, by submitting your contact information to RPSA, Inc., requesting information regarding RPSA, Inc.’s products and/or engaging in telephone conversations with any RPSA, Inc. representative, you are expressly consenting to the recordation and monitoring of all such communications. In addition, you are acknowledging and agreeing to RPSA, Inc.’s Terms of Use and Privacy Policy as set forth on this website.
ProductsRICOH Ri 100 DTG System
RICOH Ri 1000 Printer
Ricoh Ri 2000 Printer
RICOH Software
Downloads
Onsite Training
FAQ
Support
